<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaitlyn Hobbs</title>
    <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kaitlyn Hobbs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Giving Discourse.</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/the-giving-discourse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/the-giving-discourse/</guid>
      <description>Kelowna, Canada based discussion group, with meet-ups occuring in 4-week intervals.&#xA;The aim of this casual discussion group is to generate individual thinking about giving meaningfully. As we will discuss, there is no need to be in a position to give substantially; small contributions in the form of time, money, or attention has the capacity to amount to big change.&#xA;Come to share, come to listen, come as you are!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research Report: Improving access to palliative care.</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/rtp-pain-relief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/rtp-pain-relief/</guid>
      <description>As part of the Fall 2023 Research Training Program through Charity Entrepreneurship, 16 of us from across the globe met virtually to research and discuss the topic of effective giving over 11-weeks. In it, we learned ways to prioritise cause areas, compared different intervention ideas within a single cause area, and evaluated plausibility and cost-effectiveness of seemingly promising new interventions.&#xA;This report investigates the plausibility of starting a new charity that increases access to at-home palliative care in Sub-saharan Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research Report: Mass media for increasing caregiver awareness.</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/rtp-mass-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/rtp-mass-media/</guid>
      <description>As part of the Fall 2023 Research Training Program through Charity Entrepreneurship, 16 of us from across the globe met virtually to research and discuss the topic of effective giving over 11-weeks. In it, we learned ways to prioritise cause areas, compared different intervention ideas within a single cause area, and evaluated plausibility and cost-effectiveness of seemingly promising new interventions.&#xA;This report investigates the plausibility of starting a new charity that leverages mass media to increase health-seeking and health-protecting behaviours in low-middle income countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Access Measures.</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/spatial-access-measures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/spatial-access-measures/</guid>
      <description>The Spatial Access Measures (SAM) are a result of work commissioned by Infrastructure Canada to develop data and analytical frameworks for assessing the landscape of public transportation in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Database Development: Linkable Open Data Environment.</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/lode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/lode/</guid>
      <description>The Linkable Open Data Environment (LODE) is a government open data initiative to consolidate micro-data into singular, connective, geospatial databases. I contributed to the development of the LODE production pipeline and dissemination of several complete databases including:&#xA;The Open Database of Infrastructure (ODI) - May 8, 2023 — Version 1.0 The Open Database of Education Facilities (ODEF) - November 28, 2022 — Version 2.1 &amp;amp; April 9, 2021 — Version 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Local Business Conditions Index.</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/rtlbci/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/rtlbci/</guid>
      <description>Highlighting several population centres in Canada, the Real-time Local Business Conditions Index (RTLBCI) is an experimental indicator of business operations that leverages public and proprietary micro-data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capstone Project: Covid-19 Outbreak Analysis.</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/covid-19-ubco/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/posts/covid-19-ubco/</guid>
      <description>Student Capstone Project Highlight Link to heading Our team of three developed a provincial database of long‐term care (LTC) homes and modelled COVID‐19 outbreaks in British Columbia. This work, completed as part of a capstone project at The University of British Columbia (UBC) under guidance from Statistics Canada, has been highlighted by UBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a seasoned Data Scientist and Researcher with a diverse skill set and applied knowledge in spatial analysis, demographic analysis, and programmatic pipeline development. My recent participation in Charity Entrepreneurship&amp;rsquo;s Research Training Program showcases my ability to tackle complex issues in diverse domains, including mass-media strategies, pain relief accessibility, and corporate campaigning.&#xA;My expertise extends technical experience in data science to addressing social challenges. I am able to lead projects, conduct impactful and actionable research, communicate with stakeholders and engage in community initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaitlynhobbs.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>I am currently open to offers regarding contract work.&#xA;Send me a message on LinkedIn or e-mail me at khobbs3@uwo.ca.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
